export default data = [
    {
        question: "Who develop react.js?",
        options: [" Nike John","Nile","Jordan Walke"," Jordan mike"],
        correct_option: "Jordan Walke"
    },
    {
        question: "Who develop react.js?",
        options: ["Apple","Facebook","Twitter","Google"],
        correct_option: "Facebook"
    },
    {
        question: "What is used in ReactJs to increase performance ",
        options: [" Both B and c","Original DOM","Virtual DOM"," None of the above"],
        correct_option: "Virtual DOM"
    },
    {
        question: "What is state in react?",
        options: ["A prement storage","Internal storage of the component"," Both A and B"," None of the above"],
        correct_option: "Internal storage of the component"
    },
    {
        question: "Everything in react is ",
        options: ["Component"," Model","Method","Package"],
        correct_option: "Component"
    },
    {
        question: "At the highest level, React components have lifecycle events that fall into ",
        options: ["Destruction","State/Property Updates","Initialization","All of the above"],
        correct_option: "All of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "React component can return how many components",
        options: ["one","multiple","two","three"],
        correct_option: "multiple"
    },
    {
        question: "What are props into other components ",
        options: [" Injected","Both A and C","Method","None of the above"],
        correct_option: "Method"
    },
    
    {
        question: "React.js in MVC is?",
        options: ["Model","Middleware","Method","Controller"],
        correct_option: "Controller"
    },
   
    {
        question: "Must API for every ReactJs component ?",
        options: ["SetinitialComponent","renderComponent","render","All of the above"],
        correct_option: "renderComponent"
    }
    
]